<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tondauer</title>
    <link>https://tondauer.art/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tondauer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>[CC-BY-SA](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/deed.en) Copyright © 2021 by Benjamin Geer</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tondauer.art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Armande de Polignac, Preludes for Piano</title>
      <link>https://tondauer.art/2022/10/polignac-preludes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tondauer.art/2022/10/polignac-preludes/</guid>
      <description>Edition Edited by Benjamin Geer and Florence Launay. Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International licence.
Critical edition (PDF), ISBN 979-0-707186-03-9 Facsimiles of Sources EB (Bibliothèque nationale de France). Shelfmark ark:/12148/cb43209797j. This reproduction is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International license. EP (descendants of Armande de Polignac). This reproduction is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International license. Source Code Source code on GitHub</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About This Site</title>
      <link>https://tondauer.art/about-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tondauer.art/about-this-site/</guid>
      <description>What is Tondauer? Tondauer (in German, the duration of a sound) is a project that aims to support the longevity of compositions that deserve more attention than they have received. Tondauer editions are Creative Commons licensed, and are intended to allow musicians to make informed choices about interpretation.
“Many musicians &amp;hellip; have no awareness of the importance of consciously choosing an edition; which criteria to apply; which criteria may have been applied in editing; why and how to make a good choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felix Mendelssohn, Prelude Op. 104a, No. 2 (MWV U 123)</title>
      <link>https://tondauer.art/2021/03/mendelssohn-prelude-mwv-u-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tondauer.art/2021/03/mendelssohn-prelude-mwv-u-123/</guid>
      <description>Editions Edited by Benjamin Geer. Distributed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International licence.
Critical edition (PDF), ISMN 979-0-707186-01-5 Performance edition (PDF), ISMN 979-0-707186-02-2 Facsimiles of Sources A1 (Staatsbibliothek zu Berlin). Shelfmark Mus.ms.autogr. Mendelssohn Bartholdy, F. 28. Copyright © 2020 Staatsbibliothek zu Berlin. This reproduction is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International license. ES1 (Staatsbibliothek zu Berlin). Shelfmark N.Mus. 5420-1. Copyright © 2020 Staatsbibliothek zu Berlin. This reproduction is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
